<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>landmark on City23: Immoria</title><link>/tags/landmark/</link><description>Recent content in landmark on City23: Immoria</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/landmark/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Landmark: Crowder's Chowders</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-cc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-cc/</guid><description>As the river shifts, whole ecosystems of clams and unfamiliar mollusks are exposed. The Crowder family has followed these shifting waterways for generations, plucking the freshest bivalves and trivalves from their sandy homes before they go from mollusk to dry husk. Mixed with hydroponically grown veggies and the city&amp;rsquo;s freshest cream, Crowder&amp;rsquo;s Chowders give even the couriers of Immoria&amp;rsquo;s wealthiest citizens reason to slum it in the Warrens until the ladle hits the bottom of the pot.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: Sally Forth's</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-sally-forths/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-sally-forths/</guid><description>In the burned out remains of a Gear Ship dry dock the copper paneled pavillion tent covers up the burned walls and during inclement weather the dining area. The cafetiera style eating hall uses long planks of slightly burned wood as tables with huge gear teeth for seating. The food is plain fair of hearty soups cheap ale and its specialty a mixed citrus oatmeal mash that sailors believe keeps them from the sea shakes.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: The Dough/The Rise/The Bake/The Bread</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-the-bake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-the-bake/</guid><description>This bakery follows the cyclical nature of the neighborhood through the process of baking. Changing in name, appearance, menu, and smells throughout each day, this bakery is well-known for its delicious, lovingly crafted baked goods. Locals have learned which foods are available during which cycles and make sure to stop by as soon as cookies, cakes, pastries, breads, and more come out of the oven. Despite its popularity, there have been a few complaints about the crowds that tend to form outside when it is The Bake; people linger to enjoy the warmth radiating off the building and the delicious smells emanating from inside, even if they aren&amp;rsquo;t buying anything.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: The Filthy Lilt</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-filty-lilt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-filty-lilt/</guid><description>Song, music, stories, and noise in general can be heard coming from the great building that started its life as a large mill at the end of Broadway - the main road that runs through Tangent. The mill and tavern sits securely at the river&amp;rsquo;s edge. Its massive water wheel always spinning as the river passes by. Those on the other side of the river only ever hear the slow creaking of the turning wheel, and the noise from the massive building is only a barely audible murmur that sounds as if it is originating within the hearer&amp;rsquo;s head rather than from the building across the water.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: The Gong</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-gong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-gong/</guid><description>The gong, The Dinnerbell-ring, That blasted nuisance
The inventors of Brasspool are notorious for neglecting good habits in pursuit of their clockwork dreams. So, a health conscious inventor created the gong, a brass obelisk that when struck would send out ultrasonic waves reminding all it was time to eat. Unfortunately this works no matter how recently you have eaten, so it quickly became open to abuse by nefarious restauranteurs and muffin-wives.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: The Shuttered Lantern</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-shuttered-lantern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-shuttered-lantern/</guid><description>The Shuttered Lantern is a favorite haunt of people who get up early and stay up late. It&amp;rsquo;s only open when the sun isn&amp;rsquo;t up - and there are plenty of rumors about why - and so it caters to dockworkers, students, artists, artisans, and other people who tend to find their leisure in the dark hours. The beer is middling quality, middling price. But the food! The food is exquisite.</description></item><item><title>Landmark: The Spore Market</title><link>/2023/01/13/landmark-spore-market/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/13/landmark-spore-market/</guid><description>Deep under the neighborhood of the Warrens are ancient, damp tunnels, home to the region&amp;rsquo;s mushroom farms. These farms provide bushels of wholesome, flavorful mushrooms to the central neighborhood Spore Market. But in the odder corners of the Warrens, under the influence of entombed, anachronistic relics, less wholesome, but far more interesting, fungi are available.
The true name of the Spore Market lies in the smell of damp earth, and the irrepressible love of life found in the people of the Warrens.</description></item></channel></rss>