<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>person on City23: Immoria</title><link>/tags/person/</link><description>Recent content in person on City23: Immoria</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/person/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Person: Noor</title><link>/2023/02/03/person-noor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/02/03/person-noor/</guid><description>Noor (they/them) is the museum curator for The Fore. Although they think of themselves more as a caretaker or shrine keeper. They spend their time at the cramped, little desk, furiously writing tiny descriptions with their ink pen. They are sixteen years old, skinny with a short frame. They sit before an open tome, scanning the pages for stories of the past. They listen to Saga’s and Clio’s stories with rapt enthusiasm, memorizing every little detail.</description></item><item><title>Person: Saga</title><link>/2023/02/03/person-saga/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/02/03/person-saga/</guid><description>Landmark: The Dough/The Rise/The Bake/The Bread
Description: Oral storyteller, griot, and historian, Saga sits outside The Dough/The Rise/The Bake/The Bread, entertaining the crowds with her ever-changing stories. No one quite remembers how old she is, and she speaks as though she has lived through all time. Every tale she spins is different. If yesterday was all about the pride of the foolish Hero, then tomorrow will be his humility and triumph.</description></item><item><title>Person: Adair</title><link>/2023/01/21/person-adair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/21/person-adair/</guid><description>Landmark: Filthy Lilt
Description: Also known as the Oak Tree, a nickname only spoken in private by the citizens of Tangent. The owner and operator of the Filthy Lilt is a bear of a man, but always has a smile on his face - unless you get on his bad side - and tries to greet every new patron that enters the Filthy Lilt. There are rumors that he has giant blood coursing through his veins and given his enormous size, you would likely agree.</description></item><item><title>Person: Mama Crowder</title><link>/2023/01/21/person-mama-crowder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2023/01/21/person-mama-crowder/</guid><description>Landmark: Crowder&amp;rsquo;s Chowders
Description: The matron of Crowder&amp;rsquo;s Chowders, Mama Crowder is a treasure trove of knowledge about local history and fluvial patterns. If you need assistance navigating the river or the shadow politics of the Warrens, Mama can help — but her assistance comes at a cost. Don&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if you find yourself gunning for clams with the Crowder boys before sunrise.
True name: Bev / The River Mother</description></item></channel></rss>